Viewers all over the world, get ready to pray
with Prophet T.B.Joshua and loose yourself
from every bondage of sickness, limitation
and backwardness. Any moment from now, your
health will be restored and your career released
as you pray in faith with Prophet T.B.Joshua,
in Jesus' name. Viewers all over the world,
what is that bondage? Whatever bondage, begin
to free yourself! Free yourself from that
bondage, in the name of Jesus Christ! Begin
to free yourself from that bondage! Every
constant experience you are having of
that bondage, be loosed in the name of Jesus!
Every constant experience that you are having
of that bondage, be loosed in the name of
Jesus! Be released in the name of Jesus! Be
free in the name of Jesus! Open your lips
and begin to confess your freedom! I'm released!
My business is released! My health is restored!
My finances are released! My marital life
is restored! My career is released! My future
is released! In the name of Jesus Christ!
Defeat and failure are things of the past!
I'm justified! I'm no longer condemned! Open
your lips and begin to confess this! Confess
them. In the name of Jesus Christ! Change
your words and your thoughts, as a victor.
I'm justified! I'm no longer condemned! Defeat
and failure are things of the past! My health
is restored! Change your words and your thoughts.
My health has been restored! My marital life
has been restored! My career has been released!
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray! I pray you
will be sensitive to His voice and maintain
your blessings. In Jesus Christ's name we
pray. Thank You, Lord. In Jesus' name! Hallelujah!